Tang Huiyao
تانغ هوياو
Your grandpa Zhao Fengsheng is here.
جدك تشاو فنغ شنغ هنا.
Dad, are you okay?
أبي، هل أنت بخير؟
Zhao Fengsheng
تشاو فنغ شنغ
You're not dead?
أنت لست ميتاً؟
You...
أنت...
Who are you people?
من أنتم يا قوم؟
How do you have so many weapons?
كيف تمتلك كل هذه الأسلحة؟
Why so surprised?
لماذا كل هذه الدهشة؟
You know I'm with Yunting.
أنت تعلم أنني مع يونتينغ.
Isn't it normal to have a few armed brothers?
أليس من الطبيعي أن يكون لديك عدد قليل من الإخوة المسلحين؟
What the hell is Yunting?
ما هذا الهراء المسمى يونتينغ؟
Didn't my father shoot you dead?
ألم يقتلك والدي بالرصاص؟
The fortune teller said
قال العراف
my fate, Zhao Fengsheng's, is tough as nails.
مصيري، مصير تشاو فنغشنغ، قاسٍ كالصخر.
Even the King of Hell can't kill me.
حتى ملك الجحيم لا يستطيع قتلي.
What does your Tang family
ماذا عن عائلة تانغ الخاصة بك؟
have to kill me with?
ماذا يجب أن تقتلني به؟
Let's see how tough your fate really is!
لنرى مدى قسوة مصيرك حقاً!
Huiyao!
هوياو!
A puny little Tang family
عائلة تانغ صغيرة وضعيفة
dares to bully my boss?
هل يجرؤ على التنمر على مديري؟
Looking for death!
أبحث عن الموت!
I've seen plenty of mad dogs.
لقد رأيت الكثير من الكلاب المسعورة.
You, Tang Huiyao, don't qualify.
أنت يا تانغ هوياو، لست مؤهلاً.
Mu Jinfu!
مو جينفو!
Do it now!
افعل ذلك الآن!
Playing with guns against us, Yunting?
هل تلعب بالأسلحة ضدنا يا يونتينغ؟
Don't you know who the masters are?
ألا تعرف من هم الأساتذة؟
Young Master Li of Jialong.
السيد الشاب لي من جيالونغ.
Tang Hongtu.
تانغ هونغتو.
I thought you were
ظننت أنك
a proper businessman.
رجل أعمال كفء.
I never expected
لم أتوقع ذلك أبداً
you, old man, to be so cunning.
يا لك من رجل عجوز ماكر!
Young Master Li.
السيد الشاب لي.
Will you really start a war with my Tang family
هل ستشعل حرباً مع عائلة تانغ خاصتي حقاً؟
over one Zhao Fengsheng?
أكثر من تشاو فنغ شنغ؟
War?
حرب؟
Are you worthy?
هل أنت جدير؟
I admit,
أعترف بذلك،
your Li family holds immense power in Jialong.
تتمتع عائلة لي بنفوذ هائل في جيالونغ.
But this is Bian Shui.
لكن هذا هو بيان شوي.
I still have my brothers from Ghost Face Hall.
ما زلت على تواصل مع إخوتي من قاعة غوست فيس.
If we really fight to mutual destruction,
إذا تقاتلنا حقاً حتى نصل إلى الدمار المتبادل،
that wouldn't be appropriate, would it?
هذا لن يكون مناسباً، أليس كذلك؟
Second Master Tang is right!
السيد الثاني تانغ على حق!
Young Master Li,
السيد الشاب لي،
this mine contains gold worth billions.
يحتوي هذا المنجم على ذهب بقيمة مليارات.
If our two families cooperate,
إذا تعاونت عائلتانا،
with your Li family taking the lion's share,
بينما تستحوذ عائلة لي على نصيب الأسد،
your Li family
عائلة لي الخاصة بكم
will firmly suppress
سوف يقمع بشدة
Jialong,
جيالونج،
Lika,
متساوي،
and all the families in Badi.
وجميع العائلات في بادي.
Securing the top spot in the southwest!
تأمين المركز الأول في الجنوب الغربي!
You could become the richest!
قد تصبح الأغنى!
Young Master Li is amazing!
السيد الشاب لي رائع!
Young Master Li,
السيد الشاب لي،
I know Zhao Fengsheng
أنا أعرف تشاو فنغ شنغ
worked with you in Amir.
لقد عملت معك في أمير.
Will you really give up such huge profits
هل ستتخلى حقاً عن هذه الأرباح الهائلة؟
for this nobody?
لهذا الشخص المجهول؟
A nobody?
شخص مجهول؟
If my boss is a nobody,
إذا كان مديري شخصًا عاديًا،
then what am I?
إذن ما أنا؟
What are we, his Yunting brothers?
ماذا نكون نحن، إخوته في يونتينغ؟
Boss.
رئيس.
You, the esteemed Young Master Li, call him boss?
أنت، أيها السيد الشاب المحترم لي، تناديه بالرئيس؟
Just who is Zhao Fengsheng?
من هو تشاو فنغ شنغ؟
You don't even understand my boss's identity,
أنت لا تفهم حتى هوية رئيسي،
and yet you try to drive a wedge between us?
ومع ذلك تحاول أن تزرع الفتنة بيننا؟
Impossible!
مستحيل!
He, Zhao Fengsheng,
هو، تشاو فنغ شنغ
is just a small-time hoodlum who joined Yunting!
إنه مجرد مجرم صغير انضم إلى يونتينغ!
One-Eye!
عين واحدة!
Listen up!
انتبهوا!
My boss,
رئيسي،
Zhao Fengsheng,
تشاو فنغ شنغ
is the leader of Yunting's Thirteen Guards,
هو قائد الحرس الثلاثة عشر ليونتينغ،
our eternal Captain.
قائدنا الأبدي.
Captain?
قبطان؟
Impossible!
مستحيل!
He's Yunting's mysterious Captain?
هل هو قائد يونتينغ الغامض؟
Absolutely impossible!
مستحيل تمامًا!
He's just a hoodlum from Old Street!
إنه مجرد مجرم من شارع أولد ستريت!
How could he possibly be one of the Thirteen...
كيف يمكن أن يكون واحداً من الثلاثة عشر...
How could he be the Captain of the Thirteen Guards?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هو قائد الحرس الثالث عشر؟
He...
هو...
You're looking at the sky with your ass in the air,
أنت تنظر إلى السماء ومؤخرتك مرفوعة في الهواء،
blind!
أعمى!
Then you are...?
إذن أنت...؟
I am the heir of the Su family from Lika.
أنا وريث عائلة سو من ليكا.
The Su family, third of the Ten Great Families.
عائلة سو، ثالث العائلات العشر العظيمة.
I am the heir of the Yan family from Badi.
أنا وريث عائلة يان من بادي.
Heir of the Ma family from Jialong.
وريث عائلة ما من جيالونغ.
Heir of the Cao family from Lika.
وريث عائلة كاو من ليكا.
Zhao Fengsheng is...
تشاو فنغ شنغ ...
Darn it.
يا إلهي.
Even a god couldn't save us now.
حتى الإله لا يستطيع إنقاذنا الآن.
My father died right here years ago.
توفي والدي هنا منذ سنوات.
I ask you,
أنا أطلب منك،
was it you who did it?
هل أنت من فعل ذلك؟
I don't know your father.
لا أعرف والدك.
Huiyao!
هوياو!
Dad!
أب!
What time is it for this?
ما هو الوقت المناسب لهذا؟
Say it! Say it!
قلها! قلها!
Talk!
يتحدث!
I can't say it!
لا أستطيع قول ذلك!
If I talk, we all die!
إذا تكلمت، سنموت جميعاً!
Dad!
أب!
You think if you don't talk,
تظن أنه إذا لم تتكلم،
we, Yunting, won't find out?
لن نكتشف ذلك نحن يا يونتينغ؟
Stop!
قف!
I'll talk.
سأتحدث.
Your father...
والدك...
I sent people to kill him.
أرسلتُ رجالاً لقتله.
My father had no grudge against you.
لم يكن والدي يحمل أي ضغينة ضدك.
Why did you kill him?
لماذا قتلته؟
Someone...
شخص ما...
...gave me the order.
...أعطاني الأمر.
Who?
من؟
Mancheng...
مانشينج...
...the Lei Family.
...عائلة لي.
The Lei Family of Mancheng.
عائلة لي من مانتشنغ.
That's a force as rich as a nation.
إنها قوة غنية كأمة.
The Lei Family is far away in Mancheng.
عائلة لي بعيدة في مانتشنغ.
Why would they want my father dead?
لماذا يريدون موت والدي؟
Your mother was the eldest daughter of the Lei Family.
كانت والدتك الابنة الكبرى لعائلة لي.
My mother?
أمي؟
The Lei Family's eldest daughter?
الابنة الكبرى لعائلة لي؟
The one who ordered your father's death...
الشخص الذي أمر بقتل والدك...
...is your uncle.
...هو عمك.
Lei Sinian.
لي سينيان.
My uncle killed my father?
هل قتل عمي والدي؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Why?!
لماذا؟!
Your father wanted to use this gold mine...
أراد والدك استخدام منجم الذهب هذا...
...to help you seize the Lei Family heir position.
...لمساعدتك في الاستيلاء على منصب وريث عائلة لي.
He brought this upon himself.
لقد جلب هذا على نفسه.
I understand now.
فهمت الآن.
So when you assassinated my father...
إذن عندما اغتلت والدي...
...you discovered clues about the gold mine.
...لقد اكتشفت أدلة حول منجم الذهب.
I was going to use you to threaten your father...
كنت سأستخدمك لتهديد والدك...
...to force him to reveal the mine's secret.
...لإجباره على كشف سر المنجم.
But Bian Shui has many factions.
لكن بيان شوي يضم العديد من الفصائل.
I also feared the Lei Family learning of the mine.
كنت أخشى أيضاً أن تعلم عائلة لي بأمر المنجم.
That's why I plotted all this in secret.
لهذا السبب خططت لكل هذا سراً.
Now that the truth is out...
والآن وقد انكشفت الحقيقة...
...I'll send you down...
...سأرسلك إلى الأسفل...
...to apologize to my father!
...لأعتذر لأبي!
Zhao Fengsheng!
تشاو فنغ شنغ!
I planned all of this.
لقد خططت لكل هذا.
I take full responsibility for my actions.
أتحمل المسؤولية الكاملة عن أفعالي.
I don't beg for your mercy.
أنا لا أتوسل إليك أن ترحمني.
But I beg you to spare my son.
لكنني أتوسل إليكم أن ترحموا ابني.
I, Tang Hongtu...
أنا، تانغ هونغتو...
...kneel in gratitude for your great kindness.
...أركع امتناناً لكرمك العظيم.
Dad!
أب!
Those who harmed you...
أولئك الذين آذوك...
...will finally pay the price.
...سيدفع الثمن في النهاية.
Dad...
أب...
Zhao Fengsheng!
تشاو فنغ شنغ!
You'll pay for this!
ستدفع ثمن هذا!
Dad!
أب!
If I weren't so tough...
لو لم أكن بهذه القسوة...
...I'd have died by your hands long ago!
...كنت سأموت على يديك منذ زمن بعيد!
And you dare seek revenge on me?
وتجرؤ على الانتقام مني؟
Zhao Fengsheng!
تشاو فنغ شنغ!
You drove my father to his death!
لقد تسببت في وفاة والدي!
I'll take your life!
سأنهي حياتك!
Zhao Fengsheng!
تشاو فنغ شنغ!
Boss.
رئيس.
How should we handle these people?
كيف ينبغي لنا التعامل مع هؤلاء الأشخاص؟
Tang Hongtu has paid with his life.
دفع تانغ هونغتو حياته ثمناً لذلك.
But Tang Huiyao...
لكن تانغ هوياو ...
...has committed so many evils.
...ارتكب الكثير من الشرور.
We can't let him go.
لا يمكننا أن ندعه يرحل.
No!
لا!
I won't go to prison!
لن أدخل السجن!
I'm a young master of the Tang Family!
أنا سيد شاب من عائلة تانغ!
You few, carry him down.
أيها القلة، احملوه إلى الأسفل.
Zhao Fengsheng!
تشاو فنغ شنغ!
I won't go to prison!
لن أدخل السجن!
No prison!
لا سجن!
Zhao Fengsheng!
تشاو فنغ شنغ!
Brother Zhao!
الأخ تشاو!
No!
لا!
Master Feng!
خبير فينغ!
I was blind!
كنت أعمى!
I was so blind!
كنتُ أعمى تماماً!
Blind!
أعمى!
If you're still unhappy...
إذا كنت لا تزال غير راضٍ...
...gouge out my other eye too!
...أفقأ عيني الأخرى أيضاً!
One-Eye.
ذو العين الواحدة.
You have a murder case on your hands.
أنت أمام قضية قتل.
You must face legal judgment.
يجب أن تواجه حكماً قانونياً.
Legal judgment.
حكم قانوني.
Take those who followed Mu Jinfu...
لنأخذ على سبيل المثال أولئك الذين اتبعوا مو جينفو...
...and send them with him to the Bian Shui police.
...وأرسلهم معه إلى مركز شرطة بيان شوي.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Mr. Zhao, I beg you!
السيد تشاو، أرجوك!
I won't go!
لن أذهب!
I don't want to go to prison!
لا أريد الذهاب إلى السجن!
Please, let me go!
أرجوكم، دعوني أذهب!
Take him away.
خذوه بعيداً.
Mr. Zhao!
السيد تشاو!
Mr. Zhao, I won't go!
سيد تشاو، لن أذهب!
I don't want to rot in a cell!
لا أريد أن أتعفن في زنزانة!
Mr. Zhao, spare me!
يا سيد تشاو، ارحمني!
Mr. Zhao!
السيد تشاو!
Brother Fengsheng.
الأخ فنغشنغ.
Thank you for saving my life.
شكراً لك على إنقاذ حياتي.
It's because of me...
هذا بسببي...
...that you were dragged into the Tang Family conflict.
...أنك قد تم جرّك إلى صراع عائلة تانغ.
I should have protected you all.
كان عليّ أن أحميكم جميعاً.
I didn't even know...
لم أكن أعرف حتى...
...you're the captain of Yunting.
...أنت قائد سفينة يونتينغ.
Could you have guessed?
هل كنت تتوقع ذلك؟
I'm a mysterious man.
أنا رجل غامض.
I've been underestimating you all along.
لقد كنت أستهين بك طوال الوقت.
No need to apologize.
لا داعي للاعتذار.
Our Old Street doesn't have many business-savvy people.
لا يوجد في شارعنا القديم الكثير من الأشخاص ذوي الخبرة في مجال الأعمال.
The reconstruction of Old Street and the gold mine's development...
إعادة بناء شارع أولد ستريت وتطوير منجم الذهب...
...will still need the Qian Group's efforts.
...ستظل بحاجة إلى جهود مجموعة تشيان.
Regarding the gold mine...
بخصوص منجم الذهب...
...Brother Fengsheng, you can leave it to us with peace of mind.
...أخي فنغشنغ، يمكنك ترك الأمر لنا وأنت مطمئن.
The Qian Family...
عائلة تشيان...
...will definitely build you...
...سيبنيك بالتأكيد...
...a massive financial reserve.
...احتياطي مالي ضخم.
Then I thank you.
إذن أشكرك.
I'll take my leave now.
سأغادر الآن.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Boss.
رئيس.
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
You're really something now.
أنت شخص مميز حقاً الآن.
Keep talking nonsense and see what happens.
استمر في قول الهراء وانظر ماذا سيحدث.
Tian Yu.
تيان يو.
If you have something to say to Brother Zhao...
إذا كان لديك ما تقوله للأخ تشاو...
...go say it now.
...اذهب وقلها الآن.
Looking for a beating, are you?
هل تبحث عن ضرب مبرح؟
So you're Zhao Fengsheng.
إذًا أنت تشاو فنغ شنغ.
In all my life...
طوال حياتي...
...I've never seen someone as...
...لم أرَ قط شخصاً مثله...
...lacking in self-awareness...
...يفتقر إلى الوعي الذاتي...
...you lunatic!
...يا مجنون!
How can you be so narcissistic?
كيف يمكن أن تكون نرجسياً إلى هذا الحد؟
Me? Narcissistic?
أنا؟ نرجسي؟
Me?
أنا؟
You!
أنت!
You jerk!
يا لك من أحمق!
Get out of here!
اخرج من هنا!
Jerk!
هَزَّة!
Jerk! You stop right there!
يا أحمق! توقف هنا!
Tian Yu.
تيان يو.
Scoundrel
الوغد
Let go of me!
اتركني!
No matter what you do,
مهما فعلت،
your father will support you.
والدك سيدعمك.